well this hour we are here to discuss
我们这个时候在这里讨论
we're here to discuss secular counseling
我们在这里讨论世俗咨询
theories and also integration theories
理论和整合理论
and the questions that we have our first
而且，我们有我们的第一个问题
between those things and biblical
这些事与圣经之间
counseling what are the differences and
咨询有什么不同和
then beyond that do these differences
然后超出这些差异
really matter and if they matter why do
真的很重要，如果它们重要，为什么呢
they matter well rather than comparing
它们很重要而不是比较
brief sketches of many I will present
我将介绍许多简短的草图
one detailed description of a secular
一个世俗的详细描述
counselor and one of an integrationist
辅导员和整合者之一
for those of you who are well-read I
对于那些读得很好的人我
think you'll find these to be
认为你会发现这些
representative samples of each so first
首先是每个代表性的样本
I'd like us to consider secular
我希望我们考虑世俗
counselor John Bradshaw please turn to
顾问John Bradshaw请转向
page 4 in your conference notebook and
第4页，您的会议笔记本
you'll find John Bradshaw 4 for the
你会找到John Bradshaw4的
secular counselor the integrationist and
世俗顾问整合主义者和
the biblical counselor
圣经辅导员
we're going to be considering what each
我们将考虑每个人
believes and teaches about five
相信并教导大约五个
different things god man truth sin and
不同的事情神人真理的罪恶和
change so first for John Bradshaw
首先改变约翰布拉德肖
although he attended a 12-step program
虽然他参加了一个12步计划
during his mid-20s with no success in
在他20多岁时没有成功
overcoming his drunkenness John Bradshaw
克服他的醉酒约翰布拉德肖
borrowed the higher concept idea as his
借用了更高的概念理念作为他的
view for God so bradshaw's God is a
为了上帝的观点， 所以布拉德肖的上帝是一个
higher power when he was late in life he
他晚年生活中的力量更大
wrote about that higher power and that's
写下了更高的权力，那就是
the first quote in your notebook
笔记本中的第一个引用
Bradshaw higher power was this he said
他说，布拉德肖有更高的权力
my higher power is the fruit of my
我更高的力量是我的成果
subjective search for meaning coupled
主观搜索意义耦合
with my spirituality and religious faith
以我的灵性和宗教信仰
my happiness really comes from a new
我的幸福真的来自一个新的
self definition one that says you're
自我定义，说你是
worthy of whatever you honestly want and
值得你真诚想要的任何东西
can create the joy in my life right now
可以在我现在的 生活创造快乐
stems from the creative risks I've taken
源于我所承担的创造性风险
because I've believed in myself well in
因为我很好地相信自己
a similar vein Bradshaw teaches people
类似的静脉布拉德肖教人们
to worship themselves because they have
因为他们有崇拜自己
an innocent inner child in fact he
事实上，他是一个无辜的内心孩子
boldly remakes the statement of God's
大胆地重写了上帝的陈述
own identity I am that I am into a
自己的身份，我说我 成
phrase of self worship Bradshaw
自我崇拜的短语布拉德肖
instructs each person that follows his
指示跟随他的每个人
thinking to discover their own i am-ness
想着自己去发现我是岬
what does Bradshaw believe about man
布拉德肖对人的看法是什么
John Bradshaw theory is that man is
约翰·布拉德肖理论认为人是
inherently good he writes that people
天生善良的他写的人
are born with a core God likeness but
出生时有一个核心的上帝相似但是
that core god likeness is tainted by the
该核心上帝形像被污染
actions of others John Bradshaw also
其他人的行动约翰布拉德肖也
teaches that every person is
告诉我们每个人都是
self-sufficient we'll talk more about
自给自足我们会更多地谈论
that in the change section later
在 稍后的更改部分
according to Bradshaw man's basic
根据布拉德肖男子的基本情况
problem is separation from the true self
问题是与真实自我分离
that happens when people believe they
当人们相信他们时就会发生
are flawed and defective rather than
有缺陷而且有缺陷而不是
sufficient the truth he teaches is that
他所教导的真理就足够了
man is self-sufficient when a person is
一个人就是自给自足的人
separated from that concept then he
那个概念与他分开了
cannot think true thoughts John Bradshaw
想不出真正的想法John Bradshaw
recommends the examination of one's own
建议检查一个人自己
childhood to discover the sources of
童年发现的来源
current problems so what do most adults
目前的问题所以大多数成年人都有
find when they do remember their
找到他们记得他们的时候
upbringing
教养
well according to Bradshaw they discover
根据Bradshaw的说法他们发现了
the things that damaged self-esteem
那些损害自尊的事情
those are
那些是
family rules dysfunctional families
家庭规则功能失调的家庭
compulsive families addicted families
强迫性家庭上瘾的家庭
and families where sexual and physical
和性和身体的家庭
abuse have occurred in his definition of
在他的定义中发生了滥用
physical abuse that includes any
身体虐待，包括任何
corporal punishment in the following
下列体罚
paragraph which is printed in your
印在你身上的段落
notebook Bradshaw
笔记本Bradshaw
explains two terms that he invented
解释了他发明的两个术语
well-known terms - codependency and a
众所周知的术语 - 相互依赖性和
dysfunctional family environment here's
这里功能失调的家庭环境
what he says codependency is a disease
他所说的相互依赖是一种疾病
of the developing self causing various
发展中的自我造成各种各样的
degrees of D self mint I - eight the
D自我薄荷的程度我-八
word disease to indicate that
字疾病表明
codependency is not a medical condition
共同依赖不是一种医疗条件
it is a loss of ease with oneself a
它是容易 与自己一 亏损
feeling of inner emptiness a state of
内心空虚的感觉是一种状态
not being at home with oneself when we
我们不在家时与自己在一起
look at the rules of poisonous pedagogy
看看有毒教育学的规则
it seems clear that selfhood would be a
很明显，自我会是一个
unique achievement for anyone raised
任何人的独特成就
with these rules
遵守这些规则
end quote so in light of that Bradshaw
最后引用所以根据布拉德肖的说法
offers many techniques for discovering
提供了许多发现技术
vital truth about the family
关于家庭的重要真相
these include visualisation remembering
这些包括可视化记忆
secrets from the past compiling detailed
从过去的秘密编译详细
charts to diagram the heart that
图表绘制了心脏
relatives have done to each other he
亲戚彼此做了他
also recommends confronting family
还建议面对家庭
secrets and dealing with supposed
秘密和处理假设
hindrances to the development of the
拦阻 的发展
self-worth of one's inner child so in
一个人内心的孩子的自我价值
his view of man sin change and truth
他认为人的罪恶改变和真理
these things are essential for solving
这些东西对解决至关重要
life problems so Bradshaw believes that
生活问题所以布拉德肖认为
truth is found within and that it's lost
真相被发现并且它已经失去了
during childhood
在童年时期
and what about sin what does he think
而关于罪恶什么什么难道他想
about sin John Bradshaw teaches that sin
关于罪约翰布拉德肖教导罪
results from being sinned against
被犯罪的结果
sinners aren't responsible for sin they
罪人对他们的罪不负责任
are victims of toxic shame
是有毒耻辱的受害者
Bradshaw contends that the inner child
布拉德肖认为内心的孩子
of each person is pure but has been
每个人都很纯洁，但一直都是
damaged by this toxic shame this theory
受到这种毒性羞辱这种理论的破坏
denies man's responsibility for his own
否认男人对自己的责任
sin take a look at the summary of
罪看看总结
Bradshaw's belief about sin that's also
布拉德肖对罪的看法也是如此
printed in your outline here's a summary
打印在你的大纲中这里是一个总结
of his teaching he thinks that a chain
他的教学他认为是一个链条
reaction begins when parents sin which
当父母犯罪时，反应就开始了
causes their children shame this leads
导致他们的孩子羞辱这种线索
to the children's sin which in turn
对孩子的罪，反过来
later places the same destructive shame
后来发生同样的破坏性耻辱
on their own children who are then
那时他们自己的孩子
powerless to refuse temptations to sin
无力拒绝对罪的诱惑
so these are bradshaw's beliefs about
所以这些都是布拉德肖的有关信仰
sin do you think his views about sin
罪恶你认为他对罪的看法
affect how he counsels people is his
影响他如何劝告人是他的
view of sin similar to yours if not does
如果没有，那就像你的罪一样
that difference matter let's consider
这个差异让我们考虑一下
Bradshaw's teaching on change bradshaw's
布拉德肖关于改变布拉德肖的教学
view of the desired change is to reclaim
期望的变化的观点是回收
the inner child the best the subtitle of
内心的孩子是最好的副标题
John Bradshaw a best-selling book called
约翰·布拉德肖一本畅销书叫
homecoming was reclaiming and
归乡是回收和
championing your inner child
支持你内心的孩子
he teaches that you are the one who
他教导你是那个人
exalts yourself and he says that that is
提升自己，他说那就是
spiritual he claims that if you can
精神他声称， 如果你能
connect to yourself
连接到自己
including being able to be led by
包括能够被领导
feelings and desires which are good
感情和欲望是好的
then you can be healthy
那你就健康了
Bradshaw communicates his belief that
布拉德肖传达了他的信念
man is self-sufficient with a watershed
人是自给自足的分水岭
visualization tool this is one of the
可视化工具这是其中之一
landmark components of John bradshaw's
Johnbradshaw的标志性组成部分
counseling model this is how somebody he
咨询模式这是他的人
would teach should reclaim their damaged
教会应该收回他们受损的人
inner child which will result in mental
内心的孩子会导致心理上的
health here's the quote he says relax
健康在这里是他说放松的报价
and focus on your breathing imagine that
并专注于你的呼吸想象
you're walking down a long flight of
你走了很长一段路
stairs and then you go back through time
楼梯，然后你回去的时间
to a street where you lived when you
去你所居住的街道
were seven years old see a small child
七岁时看到一个小孩
coming out of the door tell him that
走出门告诉他
you're from his future tell him that you
你来自他的未来告诉他你
know better than anyone what he's been
比任何人都更了解他曾经做过的事情
through what he's suffering his
通过他的痛苦他的
abandonment and his shame now ask him if
遗弃和他的耻辱现在问他是否
he's willing to go home with you take
他愿意和你一起回家
him by the hand and start walking away
他牵着手走开了
see your mom and dad come out on the
看到你的妈妈和爸爸出来了
porch wave goodbye to them continue
门廊挥手告别他们继续
walking away until they are completely
走开，直到他们完全
gone embrace all your friends and allow
走了你所有的朋友，并允许
your higher power to come into your
你的更高权力进入你的
heart you remember what his higher power
心里你还记得他更高的力量
is we go on now walk away and promise
我们现在继续走开并承诺
your child that you will meet with him
你的孩子，你将与他见面
for five minutes each day pick an exact
每天五分钟 挑选一个确切的
time hold your child in your hand and
时间把你的孩子抱在手里
let him shrink down to the size of your
让他缩小到 你 的大小
hand place him in your heart get a sense
手把他放在心里有意义
of communion with yourself
与自己交往
and your higher power and with all
和你的更高的权力和所有
things
事
Bradshaw describes this these are his
布拉德肖描述了这些是他的
words that is the salvation of your
这是你的救赎之词
inner child
内心的孩子
he instructs people to subsequently
他随后指示人们
teach exalt and protect the inner child
教导高举并保护内心的孩子
this will produce healthy self-esteem
这将产生健康的自尊心
and therefore a successful life he says
他说，这是一次成功的人生
a common Bradshaw saying is right there
一个普通的布拉德肖说就在那里
at the bottom of the page of all the
在所有的页面底部
people you will ever know you are the
你会认识的人就是你
only one you will never lose those who
只有一个你永远不会失去那些谁
follow Bradshaw's anthropology see
按照布拉德肖的人类学看
themselves as their own Savior
他们自己作为自己的救主
instructor protector and worshipper so
指导保护者和崇拜者
what are the differences between what
什么是什么区别
secular counselors think what
世俗的辅导员想什么
integrationists believe and the
融合主义者相信和
applications of Scripture in biblical
圣经在圣经中的应用
counseling do these differences matter
咨询做这些差异很重要
and if so why do they matter next let's
如果是这样，为什么他们下一个让我们重要
consider an integrationist Gary Collins
考虑一位融合主义者加里柯林斯
dr. Collins played a foundational role
博士。柯林斯扮演了基础角色
in the advancement of Christian
在基督徒的进步中
psychology since 2002 he's led the
心理学自2002年以来他的带领
Christian coaching movement which uses
使用的基督徒教练运动
the same principles to help Christian
同样的原则，帮助基督徒
professionals achieve more the
专业人士实现更多
counseling theory of Gary Collins is
Gary Collins的辅导理论是
summarized in one word integration the
总结为一个词整合了
foundation of his teaching is his method
他的教学基础是他的方法
of combining the doctrines of the Bible
结合圣经的教义
with those of psychology
与心理学的
Gary's Collins perception of integration
加里的柯林斯对整合的看法
is found in his quotes listed under the
在他的名单中列出了
truth heading that's the third from the
真理标题这是从第三
top of the page in your notes take a
你的笔记的页面顶部 需要一个
look at Gary Collins and truth he says I
看看加里柯林斯和他说我的真相
am committed to the task of integration
我致力于整合的任务
I wanted to be reflected in my work in
我希望能够在我的工作中得到体现
my writing and in my teaching I believe
我 相信 我的写作和教学
that integration of psychology and
心理学与心理学的整合
theology is an important intellectual
神学是一个重要的知识分子
challenge
挑战
in another book he writes scholarly work
在另一本书中，他写了学术着作
has shown however that Christians and
然而，已经表明基督徒和
psychologists can learn from each other
心理学家可以相互学习
without weakening or watering down the
没有减弱或浇水
enduring truths of God's Word
上帝话语的持久真理
so Gary Collins source of truth is well
所以加里科林斯的真相来源很好
he's got to the Bible and psychology he
他有圣经和心理学
also writes on this topic of combining
还写了关于这个组合的话题
the Bible and psychology he says quote
他说引用的圣经和心理学
the Word of God never claims to have all
上帝的话从未声称拥有一切
the answers to all of life's problems do
将你所有的生活中的问题做
you believe that's true
你相信这是真的
if you don't is that an important
如果你不这样重要
difference well Gary Collins is a
差异很好，加里柯林斯是一个
professing Christian he believes in the
自称基督徒他相信
God of the Bible his God is the God of
圣经的上帝，他的上帝是上帝
the Bible he also believes that the God
圣经他也相信上帝
of the Bible uses both Christian
圣经中使用的都是基督徒
counselors and unbelievers to bring
辅导员和不信的人带来
change and healing to people in need
改变和治愈有需要的人
look at the quote there in the gods
看看众神中的引文
section of our of dr. Collins he says
我们博士的部分。柯林斯，他说
the scriptures and our own experiences
经文和我们自己的经验
give abundant evidences that God can and
提供充足的证据证明上帝可以和
does work through capable sensitive
通过有能力的敏感工作
counselors often these counselors will
辅导员经常会这些辅导员
listen give encouragement challenge
倾听鼓励挑战
thinking and employ a host of other
思考并雇佣了许多其他人
techniques that are used by both
由两个所使用的技术
Christian counselors and by those who
基督徒辅导员和那些人
are unbelievers the help that comes from
是不信的人是 来自 于帮助
caring counselors is one of the best
关怀顾问是最好的之一
ways by which our all-powerful God
我们无所不能的上帝的方式
brings change and healing in times of
在时代带来变化和治愈
need end quote
需要结束报价
so this is important this is his view of
所以这很重要， 这是他的观点
integration ISM and how it works
集成ISM 及其工作原理
next let's take a look at the Gary
接下来让我们来看看加里
Collins section unmanned Gary Collins
柯林斯部分无人驾驶加里柯林斯
believe that man is good and he believes
相信人是善的，他相信
that self esteem is useful true and an
自尊是真实有用的
important part of helping someone be
帮助某人的重要部分
healthy he explains the biblical
健康他解释了圣经
teaching about human worth affirms that
关于人类价值的教学证实了这一点
we possess great value and significance
我们拥有巨大的价值和意义
we are described as a little lower than
我们被描述为略低于
God the Bible is full of evidence that
上帝在圣经充满了证据
shows our eternal value in the sight of
显示了我们在视线的永恒价值
God and of quotes this view of man is
上帝和引用这种人的观点是
central in Gary Collins counseling model
加里柯林斯咨询模型的核心
he explains how to counsel people with
他解释了如何为人们提供咨询
what he calls inferiority feelings and
他称之为自卑感和
low self-esteem with the items on the
自尊心低的人
following list give genuine support
以下列表给予真正的支持
acceptance and approval share the
接受和批准分享
biblical perspective on self-esteem
关于自尊的圣经观点
that's at the top of the page what we
这是我们的页面顶部
just read seek to develop understanding
只是阅读寻求发展理解
and a realistic self-evaluation and
和现实的自我评价和
change unhealthy self-talk and of that
改变不健康的自我谈话和那种
quote Gary Collins is a leading
引用加里柯林斯是一个领先的
Christian psychologist his books are
基督教心理学家他的书是
used as textbooks and colleges and
用作教科书和大学
universities and grad schools that train
训练的大学和研究生院
people for Christian psychology so we've
基督教心理学的人， 所以我们
considered what he believes about God
考虑到他对上帝的看法
and man and truth how does he put those
而男人和真理他是如何把这些
beliefs into practice in his counseling
在他的咨询中将信念付诸实践
ministry for that let's look at the
那个事工让我们来看看
section on sin and change
关于罪和变化的部分
Gary Collins believes that people
加里柯林斯认为，人
including Christians require psychology
包括基督徒在内需要心理学
for resolution of their problems
解决他们的问题
he believes that Christians require
他认为基督徒需要
psychology for reso
对于reso的心理学
lucien look at look at the quotes about
lucien看看有关的报价
sin and change in the Collins outline in
罪和变化柯林斯提纲
in one of his books he talks about Jay
在他的一本书中，他谈到杰伊
Adams and he agrees with Jay Adams on
亚当斯和他同意杰伊亚当斯的观点
the topic of how to deal with sin he
关于如何处理罪恶的话题
gives quotes from Jay Adams book more
给杰伊亚当斯的报价更多
than redemption and then he says the Jay
而不是救赎，然后他说周杰伦
Adams correctly explains the Bible's
亚当斯正确地解释了圣经
mandate for dealing with sin confession
处理罪恶认罪的任务
repentance and restitution but then in
忏悔和恢复原状然后进入
the conclusion of the same chapter
同一章的结论
Collins discusses a hypothetical
柯林斯讨论了一个假设
situation and he has apparently a
情况，他显然是一个
contrary word here's what he says at the
相反的话， 这就是他所说的
end of that same chapter quote but what
同一章的结尾 引用但是什么
about people who seem addicted to their
关于那些似乎沉迷于他们的人
sinful ways people like a young man who
有罪的方式人们喜欢一个年轻人
is hooked on pornography or a person who
迷上了色情或一个人
gets drunk feels deep remorse but then
喝醉后感到深深的懊悔然后
gets drunk again
再次喝醉了
those people may confess their sins with
这些人可能会承认自己的罪过
generous genuine remorse but if you were
慷慨的真悔，但如果你是
a counselor asking if they really think
咨询员询问他们是否真的在想
they can avoid a relapse into their
他们可以避免重新进入他们的
repetitious sin probably both would say
重复的罪可能都会说
no based on their past record repeated
没有根据他们过去的记录重复
sin is likely end of quote well for the
罪很可能是报价的结尾
record I am one counselor who thinks
记录我是一个思考的顾问
that repeated sin is not likely for a
反复罪是不可能的
Christian who is relying on God
依靠上帝的基督徒
sufficient word to replace sin with
充足的词语来代替罪恶
righteousness well here's another
正义在这里是另一个
example of how integration works in
集成如何工作的示例
counseling practice this excerpt is from
咨询实践这段摘录来自
a chapter titled interpreting the Bible
一章题为解释圣经
in a Gary Collins book and so the
在加里柯林斯的书中等等
question is does the Bible answer our
问题是圣经是否回答了我们的问题
counseling questions he writes the Bible
咨询他写圣经的问题
gives no instructions to women who are
给予妇女谁没有说明
being be
是的
by their husbands this isn't surprising
他们的丈夫这并不奇怪
because the Scriptures didn't give
因为圣经没有给出
answers to every specific problem that
解决每个具体问题
might arise so we move on the client is
可能会出现所以我们继续在客户端上移动
hurting and she certainly does not need
伤害，她当然不需要
a Bible quoting judge who sends her on
一位送她的圣经引用法官
her way
她的方式
burdened with a long unrealistic to-do
背负着长期不切实际的待办事项
list that is likely to leave her feeling
名单很可能离开她的感觉
guilty and when when she doesn't put all
有罪的时候，她什么时候 不放
of the instructions into practice end of
将指令付诸实践的结束
quote
引用
so Gary Collins in his integration
所以Gary Collins在他的整合中
demonstrates a clear dichotomy between
表现出明显的二分法
counseling from the Bible and psychology
从圣经和心理学的咨询
he endorses the latter so what are the
他支持后者所以是什么
differences between secular counseling
世俗咨询之间的差异
integration ISM and the truth of the
整合ISM和真相
word as it relates to counseling issues
这个词与咨询问题有关
do those differences matter if they do
如果他们这样做，这些差异是否重要
matter why do they matter these are
事情为什么他们不管这些
vital questions for each of us next
接下来是我们每个人的重要问题
please turn to the biblical counseling
请翻到圣经辅导
page in your outline
你大纲中的页面
so what do new setec counselors believe
那么新的setec 顾问会相信什么呢？
about God man sin and change
关于神人的罪和改变
well first we believe that God is the
那么首先，我们相信上帝是
God of the Bible first of all God has
圣经的上帝首先是上帝所拥有的
power and autonomy over all his creation
权力和自主权他所有的创作
the word teaches is this from the
这个词教的是这个
beginning
开始
God created our world in Genesis 1 and
上帝在创世纪1和世界创造了我们的世界
he is sovereign over each person to the
他是在每个人主权
point where he determines when we will
他决定我们何时会这样做
live and when we will die
活着，什么时候我们会死
that's according to James 4 13 to 17
根据詹姆斯4月13日至17日的说法
also he knows each person completely you
他也知道完全每个人你
think about Psalm 139 1 through 6
思考诗篇139 1到6
one day he will destroy the heavens and
有一天他会毁灭天堂
the earth with intense heat according to
地球上有着强烈的热量
2nd Peter 3:10 God is powerful and
第二彼得3:10 神是强大的，
autonomous over his creation what about
自治区在他的创作怎么样
us has his creation well God created
我们有自己的创作以及上帝创造
everything including man for his glory
一切都包括为了他的荣耀
think about the the song of heavenly
想想天上的歌
worshipped in Revelation 4 there will be
在启示录4中受到崇拜
this praise of God you are worthy our
这是对上帝的赞美，你是值得我们的
Lord and God to receive glory and honor
主和上帝要获得荣耀和荣耀
and power for you have created all
为你创造了所有的力量
things and by your will they existed and
事情和你的意志他们存在和
were created we are created to glorify
创造了我们被创造为荣耀
God so next on your outlines we have the
上帝如此接下来在你的轮廓上我们有了
applications of worship for the
对于崇拜的应用
counseling room and that's item number 3
咨询室和那个项目编号3
under God the God of the Bible as
上帝在圣经中的上帝之下
biblical counselors we counsel for his
我们为他提供咨询的圣经辅导员
honor we study pray and prayer and pray
荣幸我们学习祈祷，祈祷和祈祷
and prepare the purpose of bringing
并准备带来的目的
glory to God we counsel with the
荣耀归给神，我们的律师与
Almighty as our primary audience not
全能的作为我们的主要受众而不是
even the counselee our aim is to speak
甚至是咨询员，我们的目标也是发言
the scriptures in a manner that pleases
经文以令人高兴的方式
God
神
we teach counsel ease to change for
我们教导律师轻松改变
godliness so that the creator will be
敬虔使创造者成为
better honored in their lives
在他们的生活中更加荣幸
what does biblical counseling believe
圣经辅导相信什么
about man man is fallen in sin can be
关于人的人在犯罪堕落可
redeemed through Jesus Christ and can be
通过耶稣基督赎回并且可以
freed from sins control the fact that
从罪恶中解脱出来控制的事实，
man is made in the image and likeness of
男人是在形象和形象
God means that man is like God and
上帝意味着人就像上帝和
represents him in some way so man was
以某种方式代表他，所以人是
created perfect or sinless but then when
创造完美或无罪然后何时
Adam sinned death and sin entered the
亚当犯了死罪，罪恶进入了
world the results of the fall of man are
世界人类堕落的结果是
that all of us are born with a sin
我们所有人都生来就有罪
nature and that each of us chooses to
自然和我们每个人都选择
sin point-three every man is dead in sin
罪恶点 - 每个人死在罪中
unless and until he is made alive with
除非及直至他是由活着
Christ by the gift from God of saving
基督借着拯救上帝的恩赐
faith in Jesus Christ and so for the
对耶稣基督的信仰，因此对于
Soul redeemed by the sacrifice of Jesus
灵魂被 耶稣的牺牲所赎回
Christ enjoys forgiveness and is no
基督享受宽恕而不是
longer a slave to sin this is so
不再是奴仆 是这样
important in counseling but romans 6
在咨询中很重要但罗马人6
teaches us that in christ we are no
告诉我们，在基督里我们不是
longer slaves of sin we are what slaves
更长的罪恶奴隶我们是奴隶
of righteousness and also Romans 8:13
正义和罗马书8:13
tells us that the Ministry of the
告诉我们，该部
indwelling Holy Spirit is that he
内住圣灵就是他
enables us to put to death the deeds of
使我们能够处死的事迹
the flesh this is the core of biblical
肉体这是 圣经的核心
counseling this is the theological
辅导这是神学
doctrine of sanctification it is a great
成圣的教义是伟大的
privilege to sit with believers and go
有权与信徒坐在一起去
over these truths and then see God use
超过这些真理，然后看到上帝使用
his word to enable them to put off sin
他的话使他们能够推迟犯罪
and put on righteousness to put to death
并且将正义置于死地
the deeds of the flesh by the Holy
神圣的肉体行为
Spirit and to resolve the life problems
精神和解决生活问题
that they came in with
他们进来了
how people perceive life problems and
人们如何看待生活问题和
solutions is directly connected to their
解决方案与他们的直接相关
beliefs about man those who believe that
对那些相信那些人的信仰
man is good seek to solve human problems
男人善于寻求解决人类的问题
with man based philosophies what else
以人为本的哲学还有什么
would that person do we who believe the
那个人会相信我吗？
Bible's description of man see the
圣经对人的描述见
unsaved man as guilty of thin and in
未得救的男子因为瘦弱而无罪
need of regeneration we believe that
需要再生我们相信
Christians can overcome sin through the
基督徒可以通过犯罪来克服罪恶
sufficient scriptures and the power of
足够的经文和权力
the Holy Spirit the truth we see as
圣灵是我们所看到的真理
biblical counselors we see the truth as
圣经辅导员我们将真理视为
the truth of the Bible truth is only
圣经真理的真理只是
found in the word and the truth that
发现在这个词和真相中
Christians need for their life problems
基督徒需要他们的生活问题
is found in the Word of God let's look
在神的话语中找到了让我们看看
at some details of that first the
在 第一个的 一些细节
inspiration of origin and origin of
灵感的起源和起源
scripture Scripture emanated from within
经文从内部散发出来
the very being of God and then the
上帝的存在然后是
authority of scriptures Wayne Grudem
经文权威Wayne Grudem
wrote in his systematic theology quote
在他的系统神学引文中写道
the authority of Scripture means that
圣经的权威意味着
all the words in scripture are God's
经文中的所有单词都是上帝的
words in such a way that to disbelieve
用不相信的方式说出的话
or disobey any word of Scripture is to
或者不遵守圣经的任何一个词
disbelieve or disobey God if that's true
如果那是真的，就不相信或不服从上帝
then that makes the Word of God the
那就是上帝的话语
source for all good counsel and I
所有好律师的来源和我
believe that it is since we can know the
相信这是因为我们可以知道
words of God the philosophies of man are
上帝的话语是人的哲学
rendered inconsequential another crucial
无关紧要的另一个至关重要
point about the Bible is number four the
关于圣经的观点是第四位的
Bible's unique incision into the soul
圣经对灵魂的独特切口
Hebrews 4 12 and 13 tells us that God
希伯来书4 12和13告诉我们上帝
discloses the motives of men's hearts
揭示了男人心中的动机
through his word no other person or
通过他的话，没有其他人或
thing could judge the heart the motives
事情可以判断心脏的动机
the desires of another man but in
另一个人的欲望，但在
counseling in biblical counseling if
在圣经咨询中提供咨询
we're looking at Scripture and God
我们正在看圣经和上帝
discloses that man's heart
透露了男人的心
to him and he's willing to tell me about
对他而言，他愿意告诉我
it and then I can then I can answer the
它然后我可以然后我可以回答
questions from the word how does the
来自这个词的问题是怎么回事
word address those desires and motives
这个词解决了那些欲望和动机
how can God help this man change those
上帝怎么能帮助这个人改变那些呢
desires into desires that bring glory
渴望带来荣耀的欲望
and honor to God number five the Word of
和荣誉神五号的话
God is the essential tool for changed
上帝是改变的必要工具
for godliness
因为敬虔
psalm 119 verses 9 through 11 tells us
诗篇119节9到11节告诉我们
that how can a young man keep his way
一个年轻人如何能够保持自己的方式
pure by keeping it according to the word
根据这个词保持纯洁
this is the power of God for change and
这是上帝要改变的 动力 和
so that's why the scriptures are the
所以这就是经文的原因
focal point of biblical counseling
圣经辅导的焦点
finally with the biblical counselor what
最后与圣经辅导员一起做什么
do we believe about sin we believe the
我们相信犯罪吗？
doctrine of Marty ology the doctrine of
Marty ology 学说的学说
Hammar theology here are the main points
这里的哈马尔神学是主要观点
of this theology unbelievers are slaves
这种神学不信的人是奴隶
to sin therefore counsel to the unsaved
因此犯罪为未得救的人提供劝告
consists of evangelism Romans 8:6 2:8
罗马书8：6 2：8传福音
says that the unbeliever is a slave to
说，不信的人是奴隶
sin and they aren't even able to please
罪恶，他们甚至无法取悦
God so that's why evangelism is the
上帝所以这就是传福音的原因
solution to the problem there are some
解决问题的方法有一些
exceptions if their life may not last
例外，如果他们的生命可能不会持续
much longer we'll talk about that more
更长的时间，我们会谈论更多
tomorrow but outside of the severe
明天但 在严重之外
exceptions we want this person to hear
我们希望此人听到的例外情况
the gospel so that they can become a
福音使他们成为一个
person who can have victory over sin new
能够战胜罪恶的人
life in Christ creates the ability for a
在基督里的生活创造了一种能力
soul to have victory over sin
灵魂战胜罪恶
1st Peter 2:1 through 3 says that we
彼得前书2：1到3说我们
grow in respect to salvation through the
通过这种方式在救赎方面成长
word also 0.3 the Christian through the
字也0.3基督徒通过
power of the scriptures and the
经文和权力
indwelling Spirit is able to overcome
内住精神能够克服
sin the certain promise also
也犯了某个应许
sanctification or changing from sin
成圣或改变罪恶
toward righteousness is the occupation
正义就是占领
of every believer until we
直到我们每个信徒
home with Christ that's what Ephesians
与基督一起回家，这就是以弗所书
4:22 says that's what we do between
4:22说这就是我们之间的所作所为
salvation and glorification between the
拯救和荣耀之间
day we were justified in the day were
一天，我们的日子是合理的是
glorified we're making progress in
荣耀我们正在进步中
sanctification we do that through the
成圣我们通过这种方式做到这一点
word we do that by putting to death the
我们这样做是通过处死来实现的
deeds of the flesh so the new thetac
肉体的事迹，所以新的thetac
counselor teaches these truths of who
辅导员讲述了谁的真相
Marty ology and confidently teaches
Marty ology并自信地教导
Christian counsel ease with the
基督徒的建议轻松自如
expectation of victory over sin so the
期待战胜罪恶所以
result of that is change true believers
那结果是改变真信徒
overcome sin the change of
克服罪恶的变化
sanctification provides assurance that a
成圣提供了保证
person is saved Millard Erikson wrote
米拉德· 埃里克森写道，人得救了
this in his systematic theology he said
他说，这在他的系统神学中
quote the genuineness of the faith that
引用信仰的真实性
leads to justification becomes apparent
导致理由变得明显
in the results which issue from it if
在结果中发出如果
there are no good works there has been
有没有好的作品出现了
no real faith or justification so the
没有真正的信仰或理由所以
true Christian in dwelled by the Holy
真正的基督徒居住在神圣的世界
Spirit and by Jesus Christ has the
精神和耶稣基督有
ability to have victory over sin this
能否战胜罪恶
process of systematically replacing sin
系统地取代罪恶的过程
with righteousness is really the
仁义是真的
essential dynamic of biblical counseling
圣经辅导的基本动力
so what are the differences between the
那么之间有什么区别呢？
counseling theories of secular
世俗的咨询理论
counselors of integrationists and
融合主义者和顾问
biblical counselors do you have a
圣经辅导员你有吗？
clearer view of them than you did about
他们比你做的更清楚
a half-hour ago and do these differences
半小时前，做这些差异
matter and if they matter why do they
问题，如果他们重要，为什么他们
matter these are the important questions
重要的是这些是重要的问题
for this hour
这一小时
well let's summarize what we've seen so
好吧，让我们总结一下我们所见过的
far if you want to you might even have
如果你想要你甚至可能有
each of the pages sitting in front of
每个页面坐在前面的
you side by side but here's a summary
你并排， 但这是一个总结
secular counseling does not
世俗咨询没有
find God as the God of the Bible we also
我们也发现上帝是圣经的上帝
saw that regarding man both secular
看到那个男人都是世俗的
counseling and integration ISM believe
咨询和整合ISM相信
that man is basically good unsaved man
那人基本上都是善良的未得救的男人
is basically good the biblical counselor
基本上是圣经辅导员
sees him as dead in sin secular
看他在世俗的罪中死了
counseling has a clear source for truth
咨询有明确的事实来源
and where is that it's it's found within
它是在哪里发现的
integration is impaired is truth in both
整合受损是两者的真相
the Bible and psychology biblical
圣经和心理学圣经
counseling believes that the Bible is
咨询认为圣经是
the only source of truth secular
世俗的唯一真理来源
counseling integration ISM do have
咨询整合ISM确实有
somewhat similar views to each other
彼此有些相似的看法
regarding sin and change while biblical
关于罪和在圣经中改变
counseling holds a much different view
咨询有着截然不同的观点
on what sin is and on what type of
什么是罪，什么类型的
change should be sought in the council
应该在理事会中寻求改变
lee's life so do these differences
李的生活也是如此
really matter I believe that they do why
真的很重要我相信他们为什么这样做
do they matter they matter because
他们是否重要，因为
people in your church go to counseling
你教会的人去咨询
they go to get direction from life they
他们从生活中获取方向
will hear from their counselor answers
将听取他们的顾问答案
to the key questions of life what is my
生活中的关键问题是什么
purpose what really is my problem what's
目的是什么真的是我的问题是什么
the solution to it what should I be what
解决它应该是什么
should i try to become how should they
我应该试着成为他们应该如何
change into what should they change
改变他们应该改变什么
where is God in all this counselors have
所有这些辅导员都有上帝在哪里
answers for that question too
这个问题的答案也是如此
so which type of counseling do you
你有哪种咨询方式？
desire for the people of your church
对教会人民的渴望
that's that's really the question well
这是这是真正的问题提得好
before we go on I'd like to answer a
在我们继续之前，我想回答一个问题
couple of questions that were raised
提出了几个问题
earlier by dr. Collins first does the
博士早些时候。 柯林斯首先做到了
Bible claim to have all the answers to
圣经声称拥有所有的答案
all of life's problems I think it does
我认为它所有的生活问题
for the Christian second Timothy 3:16
因为基督徒第二提摩太后书3:16
and 17 makes this claim all Scripture is
并且17使所有经文成为这个主张
inspired by God and profitable for
受到上帝的启发并且有利可图
teaching reproof correction and training
教学责备改正和训练
and righteousness and what's the result
和正义，结果是什么
that the man of God may be adequate
上帝的 人 得以完全
equipped for every good work including
适合每一项好工作，包括
the good works God has planned for this
上帝为此计划的善行
day in these circumstances of that
在这种情况下的那一天
counsel Lee's life further the victory
律师李的生活进一步取得了胜利
Jesus Christ has won over sin equips
耶稣基督赢得了罪孽装备
every Christian to overcome sin let's
每个基督徒胜过罪恶，让我们
consider Romans 6 10 through 12 it says
考虑罗马人6 10到12 它说
the death that he died speaking of
他死后说的死亡
Christ he died to sin once for all but
基督他一劳永逸地为罪而死
the life that he lives he lives to God
他所生活的生活，他生活在上帝面前
even so consider yourselves he's telling
即便如此，你也要考虑他自己
Christians what we should think about
基督徒我们应该考虑什么
ourselves here even so consider
我们自己在这里考虑
yourselves to be dead to sin but alive
自己是死的罪，但活着
to God in Christ Jesus
基督耶稣里的上帝
most counseling problems are sin sexual
大多数咨询问题都是罪性
immorality preoccupation with control
不道德的专注于控制
drunkenness lust lying anger fear of man
醉酒欲望生气，害怕男人
all these things are identified by the
所有这些东西都是由
Bible as sin so Romans 6 teaches a much
圣经是罪，所以罗马书6教导了很多
different idea about the power of sin
关于罪的力量的不同观点
then Gary Collins description of
然后加里柯林斯的描述
Christians who quote seem addicted to
引用的基督徒似乎沉迷于
their sinful ways
他们有罪的方式
end of quote in Romans 6:11 God's Word
在罗马书6:11引用上帝的话语
is telling us what we should think about
告诉我们应该考虑什么
ourselves we are dead to sin and alive
我们自己已经死于罪恶和活着
to God that is good news for the
上帝， 是好消息
counselee who's struggling with one of
咨询谁正在与其中一个挣扎
those sins I just mentioned or any other
我刚刚提到的那些罪或其他任何罪
sin well some counseling problems are
罪过一些咨询问题
not sin and that's an important
不是罪，这是重要的
distinction we need to figure out which
区别我们需要弄清楚哪个
is which first Thessalonians 5:14
是帖撒罗尼迦前书5:14
identifies some struggling Christians as
将一些苦苦挣扎的基督徒视为
faint-hearted or weak the grand truths
胆怯或虚弱的真相
of theology and the promises of hope
神学和希望的承诺
from the scriptures equips the
从经文装备
faint-hearted and weak to grow in Christ
在基督里成长的人是胆小的，软弱的
and to overcome adversity their problem
并克服逆境他们的问题
is in sin maybe they're just weak in
在罪中也许他们只是弱者
faith maybe they're weak in their
信仰也许他们的弱点
understanding of these truths of the
了解这些真相
word maybe they're faint-hearted they've
字也许他们胆怯，他们已经
been struggling and they're not sure
一直在挣扎，他们不确定
what the Bible says about their
圣经对他们说的话
situation maybe those truths in that
情况也许是那些真相
booklet that you got tonight hope from
你今晚得到的小册子
God's Word maybe they don't really
上帝的话可能他们并不是真的
realize those or maybe they just don't
意识到那些或者他们只是没有
understand how those pertain to how life
了解那些与生活有关的方式
is today the difficult circumstances
今天是困难的情况
that they're in
他们在
well in fact 2nd Timothy 3:16 and 17
事实上， 提摩太后书3:16和17
does teach that the Bible quips
并教导圣经妙语连珠
Christians for every good work
每个好工作的基督徒
no matter the complexity or the
无论复杂性还是复杂性
circumstances what a joy it has been to
这种情况真是太棒了
see that in the last 15 years of sitting
看到在过去15年的坐着
across from Christians with all the
与所有的基督徒对面
problems that there are in life and to
问题存在于生活，
find God's Word always sufficient well
找到上帝的话总是充足的
next what about the second question dr.
接下来第二个问题博士。
Collins raised does the Bible talk about
柯林斯提出了圣经所说的话
how to counsel a wife who is being
如何为正在生活的妻子提供咨询
beaten by her husband and the husband -
她的丈夫和丈夫殴打-
regarding his serious sin absolutely in
绝对对他的严肃罪
difficult cases like this Matthew 18 15
这样的困难案例马太福音18 15
to 17 describes the course of action for
至17描述了行动的过程
the church elders
教会长老
for restoring the husband to becoming a
对于丈夫恢复成为一个
man who does obey God confront his sin
遵守上帝的人正面对他的罪
and if he doesn't repent discipline him
如果他不悔改训练他
further first John three sixteen to
进一步约翰三十六到
eighteen demands tangible health and
十八岁要求有形的健康和
protection for that woman and those
保护那个女人和那些人
children help that can be given by the
孩子可以帮助
elders men in the church and also by
在教会和长老也由 男人
church families Romans 13:1 through four
教会家庭罗马书13：1到4
endorses the use of the laws of our
赞同使用我们的法律
country to protect that woman and also
国家为了保护那个女人，也
as has happened at our church women
正如我们教会的女人们所发生
trained in biblical counseling will
受过圣经辅导训练的人会
provide the hope and comfort
提供希望和安慰
that this woman needs who has been
这个女人需要的是谁
sinned against in such a detestable way
以这种可憎的方式犯罪
I'd like to address another point
我想谈谈另一点
biblical counselors unlike the secular
与世俗不同的圣经辅导员
or Christian psychologists do not
或基督教心理学家没有
counsel the Christian and the unbeliever
劝告基督徒和不信的人
in the same way when an unbeliever comes
以不信的人来的同样方式
to the valley Bible counseling center
到山谷圣经咨询中心
for help we do start with the gospel why
为了帮助我们从福音开始为什么
because today he is what we all once
因为今天他就是我们曾经的一切
were dead in sin Ephesians 2:1 through
在以弗所书2：1到 罪中死了
three describes all of us before we were
3描述了我们所有我们之前
saved dead in trespasses and sins
在过犯罪恶中拯救了死者
following the course of this world
跟随这个世界的进程
following the Prince of the power of the
继王子的力量之后
air the spirit that is now at work in
播放现在正在工作的精神
the sons of disobedience carrying out
不服从的开展儿子
the desires of the body and of the mind
身体和心灵的欲望
and they are by nature children of Wrath
他们是由 怒之子
Romans 6:17 calls the unbeliever a slave
罗马书6:17称不信的人为奴隶
to sin I'm here to tell you tonight that
罪我在这里要告诉你今晚
if somebody is dead in sin or somebody
如果有人死于罪或某人
is a slave to sin I think there is one
是罪的奴隶我认为有一个
answer to that problem that is
回答那个问题
redemption through the blood of Jesus
通过 耶稣 的血来救赎
Christ amen
基督阿门
that is their need well one of the great
这是他们需要的伟大之一
joys every year at our biblical
每年都在圣经中欢乐
counseling center is the conversion of
咨询中心是转换
counsel ease let me tell you about one
律师轻松让我告诉你一个
guy Matt he had been around the church
马特，他曾经在教堂附近
he had attended for a while
他参加了一段时间
but he was not a believer he was an
但他不是一个信徒， 他是一个
angry man and his wife had left him
愤怒的男人和他的妻子离开了他
because he was an angry man in the first
因为他是一个愤怒的人在第一
session he was telling me all the
会议他告诉我所有的
problems and I started showing him
问题，我开始向他展示
Ephesians 5 and what God requires of a
以弗所书5和神需要的
Christian husband he said I'm not that
基督徒的丈夫，他说我不是那个
man I've never been that man we went
男人， 我从来没有去过那个男人
further with that he knew the gospel he
进一步，他知道他的福音
wanted to be in heaven rather than hell
想要在天堂而不是地狱
at the end of this life but he had never
在这生命的最后，但他从来没有
repented of his life of sin turning to
悔改了他的罪恶生活转向
Christ as Lord even though he did
基督作为主， 即使他做了
believe in the facts of the gospel that
相信福音的事实
night he prayed he did repent and
晚上他祈祷他确实悔改了
express his faith in the facts of the
表达他对事实的信念
gospel what a joy what a joy well
福音是多么快乐， 多么快乐
subsequently we saw God do what only he
后来我们看到上帝只做他的事
can do not only save that man but he
除了他，他不仅可以拯救那个人
became the most incredibly patient man
成为最令人难以置信的耐心的人
sometimes I was at his house when he had
有时我在他家时，他
conversations with his wife and she she
和他的妻子和她谈话
would yell at him for 10 minutes
会对他大喊10分钟
non-stop and not yelling like you can
不停的，不要像你一样大喊大叫
hold the phone next to your ear for the
将手机放在耳边的旁边
10 minutes she was very angry at him
10分钟，她对他非常生气
because of the ways that he had sinned
因为他犯了罪的方式
against her as time went by she realized
随着时间的推移，她意识到了她
he was a different man and she came back
他是另一个男人，她回来了
and then not too long after that she
然后不久，她
committed her life to Christ she
致力于她的生活，她的基督
repented and believed it was such a joy
悔改并相信这是一种快乐
to participate in the baptism of this
参加这个洗礼
man and woman this is years ago they're
男人和女人这是几年前他们是
still at our church they're involved in
还在我们教堂，他们参与其中
ministry and what a what a beautiful
事工和多么美好
thing to see God change to people
看到上帝改变了人的 事情
through his word
通过他的话
so it's the gospel and then it's the
所以这是福音，然后才是
word of helping them put off all these
帮助他们推迟所有这些
patterns of sin that they have been
他们曾经犯过的罪恶模式
living with and have what they have now
和他们一起生活并拥有他们现在所拥有的
a great marriage of living the
生活的 伟大婚姻
husband-and-wife roles of Ephesians 5
以弗所书5的夫妻角色
god is good
上帝是好的
well I'd like to address four groups of
好吧，我想谈谈四组
people and there are probably members of
人们可能有成员
each of these four groups in this
这四组中的每一组都在此
building right now first for the
现在首先建造
Christian counselor who practices
实践的基督徒辅导员
integration ISM I just appeal to you
整合ISM我只是呼吁你
study the Scriptures consider these
研究圣经考虑这些
things be consistent in your own
事情在你自己的一致
personal time of studying the word spend
学习单词花费的个人时间
some time with a good systematic
有一段时间具有良好的系统性
theology talking about man and sin and
神学谈论男人和罪恶和
consider what the word says about these
考虑什么话说这些
topics find a biblical counsellor sit in
主题找到一位圣经辅导员坐在里面
on a few sessions see what is going on
在几个交易日看是怎么回事
there what the goal of the biblical
有什么圣经的目标
counsellor is how they go about it what
辅导员是他们如何去做什么
is the role of the word in the Lord in
是主在这个词中的作用
those sessions the bottom line of it I
这些会议的它的底线我
say to you is study the scriptures and
对你说是研究经文和
then just between you and God come to a
然后就在你和上帝之间来到了
conclusion what do you believe and what
结论你相信什么，什么
do you believe would most glorify God in
你相信最能荣耀上帝吗？
the counsel you give to people for the
律师你给人们的
rest of your life second what about the
你的余生第二个怎么样
pastor or the elder who has referred
牧师或已提到的长老
struggling people in your own
你自己挣扎的人
congregation to secular counselors and
世俗顾问和
to integrationists that's probably most
对可能最多的融合主义者而言
pastors in America
美国的牧师
well my request to you is this find find
我对你的要求就是这个发现
some people who are either currently in
有些人目前在
therapy or have been in the past and ask
治疗或曾经过去问过
them two questions what did the
他们有两个问题
counselor say about God man sin and
辅导员说上帝的罪和罪
change and then ask them what was the
改变，然后问他们是什么
counselor source of truth
辅导员的真相来源
and then just decide what you believe
然后决定你相信什么
will best serve the sheep in your flock
最好地为你羊群中的羊群服务
from this time forward well third what
从这个时候前进到第三个什么
about the pastor or elder who is
关于牧师或老人是谁
convinced that biblical counseling is
确信圣经辅导是
what your people need my encouragement
你的人民需要我的鼓励
to you is I think a great first thing to
对你来说，我认为这是第一件好事
do is pursue becoming an anchor you'll
做就是追求成为你的锚
find out more about this during this
在此期间了解更多相关信息
weekend and also online at night org but
周末， 您也可以从晚上组织，但
the rigors of study required for that
研究针对所需要的苛刻条件
process and the time where you get to
过程和你到达的时间
talk on the phone every week with with a
每周与电话交谈
John Street or another fellow at neg to
约翰街或其他同事
help you become great at counseling from
帮助你在咨询方面变得更好
the Scriptures is worth it I'd encourage
圣经是值得的，我鼓励
you also find a few people who think the
你也找到了一些人的想法
same way who seem like they could be
同样的方式似乎他们可能
gifted men and women in counseling
有天赋的男女咨询
others and take them with you as far as
其他人，并把他们与你尽可能
you can through that process and then
你可以通过那个过程然后
just do what I think you're probably
做我认为你可能做的事情
already going to do take all the truths
已经采取了所有的事实
from the word that that you're thinking
从词，你在想
through this weekend and put them into
通过这个周末并把它们放进去
practice more in your discipleship and
在你的门徒锻炼的
counseling ministries and last church a
辅导部和最后的教会a
tender who is convinced that you want to
温柔谁相信你想要
be a biblical counselor item number one
成为圣经辅导员项目的第一名
is be consistent in your own time in the
在你自己的时间里是一致的
word first apply the word to yourself
这个词首先应用于自己
seek God's strength to put off sins and
寻求上帝的力量来推迟罪恶
put on righteousness and the things that
穿上正义和那些东西
you struggle with I was in the first M
你挣扎我是在第一个M
ABC program in 1996 and our classes were
在1996年美国广播公司节目，我们的课程是
on Saturday mornings but on Monday and
星期六早上，但周一和
Wednesday night and so I would leave the
星期三晚上，我会离开
Masters College at 10:00 at night and I
大师学院晚上10点和我
get home at about 11:00 and I couldn't
大约11点回家，我不能
go to sleep for an hour and a half after
睡了一个半小时后
that because I had things that I needed
因为我有我需要的东西
to do differently because of the truth
因为真相而采取不同的做法
of God's Word and then I tell my wife
上帝的话，然后我告诉我的妻子
the next day we need to do things
第二天 ，我们需要做的事情
differently and being the great woman of
不同的是，成为伟大的女人
God she said let's let's study the word
上帝，她说让我们来研究一下这个词
together
一起
and let's do that it was a great help in
让我们这样做是非常有帮助的
our own walks with God and in the
我们自己的散步与神，并在
relationships we had in teaching and
我们在教学和教学方面的关系
training our children so start with
训练我们的孩子，所以开始
using these things in your own life and
在你自己的生活中使用这些东西
then be consistent in the spiritual
然后在精神上保持一致
disciplines in your own walk with God
你自己与上帝同行的纪律
and then find an elder of your church
然后找到你教会的长老
and ask them about the possibilities of
并询问他们的可能性
starting to counsel within the local
开始在当地提供咨询
body well what are the differences
身体有什么不同
between the counseling theories of
在咨询理论之间
secular counselors of integrationists
融合主义者的世俗顾问
and of biblical counselors there are
还有圣经辅导员
some big ones do they matter and if so
一些大的他们是否重要，如果是的话
why do they matter I'll tell you why
为什么他们重​​要我会告诉你为什么
they matter they matter because God
他们重要， 因为上帝
reveals particular truths about himself
揭示了关于自己的特定真理
man truth sin and change and the purpose
人的真理罪与变化和目的
that you and I have every day we are on
我和你每天都在这里
this earth is to bring glory to God and
这个世界是要为上帝带来荣耀
so in our own walk with him and in our
所以在我们自己走了，并在我们的
ministry to precious brothers and
教育部珍贵的兄弟
sisters that he brings across our path
姐妹们，他带来了我们的道路
we need to glorify him that's why these
我们需要荣耀他，这就是为什么
differences matter let's become great by
差异问题让我们变得伟大
God's grace and by the work of the Holy
上帝的恩典和圣洁的工作
Spirit and enabling us to put to death
精神，使我们能够处死
the deeds of the plot of the flesh let's
肉体情节的行为让我们的
become great at honoring God at
在尊重上帝方面变得伟大
systematically replacing sin with
系统地用罪取代罪
righteousness and let's become great at
正义，让我们变得伟大
being able to love the way Christ loves
能够爱基督所爱的方式
when hurting brothers and sisters come
当伤害兄弟姐妹来的时候
to us for help let's become great at
向我们求助， 让我们变得更加优秀
being able to communicate the truth of
能够传达真相
God's Word so the guide can help that
上帝的话语，导游可以帮助你
person deal with their problems
人处理他们的问题
you
您